studentcity.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy | StudentCity

#### Overview

This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of StudentCity (“Company”, “We” or “us”). If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact as indicated in the "How to Contact Us" section below. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes.

This Privacy Policy applies to our website located at Studentcity.com and any of our other sites that link to this Privacy Policy. We refer to all of these sites as the “Website.”

#### How We Collect Information

We collect two basic types of information: personal information and anonymous information. We define “personal information” as information that is unique to an individual. Personal information might include: names, ages, contact information, payment information, school affiliation and travel schedule and preferences. Anonymous information is information that is not unique to you, such as technical information about your computer or statistical information about groups of our users.

We collect both personal information and anonymous information through the Website. We sometimes collect personal information and anonymous information by asking you to enter it into forms on our Website. For example, if you make a request for more information about one of our trips, we request your name, e-mail, phone number, the name of your school and other details.  We also collect anonymous information automatically as you use the Website—see the section below titled Cookies and Analytics

#### How We Use Your Information

If we do receive your personal information, we will only use it for the purposes described where it is collected or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, if you request more information about a trip, we will use your contact details to send you that information.

We will not share your personal information with third-parties unless:  
•    you give us your express permission to do so;  
•    it is to your parent or guardian if you are a minor;  
•    it is to your trip organizer, if you are part of a group trip;  
•    it is necessary to allow our service providers or agents to provide services for us;  
•    it is necessary in order to provide our products or services to you or to contact you;  
•    it is to other members of the Travelopia Group of companies;  
•    subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements;  
•    in connection with the sale of our business;  
•    it is necessary to process payments from you;  
•    it is necessary to investigate potential fraud or security breaches; or  
•    otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.

In addition, we may disclose anonymous information to third-parties for marketing and other business purposes. For example, we may provide information to advertisers and commercial partners about the size and demographic composition of our user base.

#### Contests, Sweepstakes and Other Promotions

We may feature contests, sweepstakes or other promotions on our Website from time to time. These promotions may require you to provide personal information in order to join and we may use this information to administer the promotion. We may also may use the information you provide to market our products and services to you. We may also share this information with our partners who may use such information to communicate with you about the contests, sweepstakes or other promotions or their products and services.

#### Marketing Communications

With your permission, we may from time to time contact you with information on offers of goods and services, brochures, new products and forthcoming events. You can sign up for these communications when you submit a form on our website. In some instances, this option will be included by default when you click the submit button. If, however, you sign up to receive communications on your mobile phone by SMS text message, this option will not be included by default.

You may opt-out of receiving marketing communications at any time.  You may opt out of receiving emails by emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#92fbfcf4fdd2e1e6e7f6f7fce6f1fbe6ebbcf1fdffade1e7f0f8f7f1e6afd7fff3fbfeb7a0a2dde2e6bfdde7e6) or by following the opt-out the instructions in our marketing e-mails. You may opt out of receiving text messages by [texting STOP to 57682].  Please allow us a reasonable time to process unsubscribe requests.

#### E-mail

We appreciate your e-mailed feedback, questions and comments. Please see the “How To Contact Us” section of this Privacy Policy. If you e-mail us, we will keep a copy of your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns and may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it once it is no longer needed.

#### Cookies and Analytics

Our website uses “cookies”—small files that permit our Website to identify your computer or mobile device on future visits. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies but certain features on our Website that use cookies may be unavailable.

We use cookies to keep track of the pages you visit on the Website and to store information about you or your preferences between visits to the Website. For example, if you click the “remember me” checkbox on our login form, the Website will set a cookie on your browser or mobile device so that you do not need to login on future visits.

We also collect anonymous information about your computer or mobile device when you use our Website such its IP address, operating system and browser type. If you follow a link to our Website or use a search engine to access our Website, we may collect the address of the page or the search engine query that referred you to our Website. We use this information to help us operate and improve the Website and to understand how visitors find our Website. For example, if we determine that you are on a mobile device, we may refer you to the mobile version of our Website.

We also use your IP address to determine the general physical location of your computer or mobile device and the name of your internet service provider.

Certain pages on our Website contain “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs) or tracking scripts. These web beacons or tracking scripts allow third-parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and any information in cookies set by the third party.

#### Third Party Advertisers

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may obtain anonymous information such the IP address of your computer or mobile device, the location of the page on which the ad appears, the time the page containing the ad was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and any information in cookies set by the third party. Our advertisers use this information to display ads for goods and services that may be of interest to you on this Website and on other websites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit: [Third Party Advertiser Information Page].

#### Links to Other Websites

For your convenience, we may provide links to other websites and web pages that we do not control. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites or pages not under our control and we do not endorse any of these websites or pages, the services or products described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or pages.

#### Third Party Social Media Platforms

The Website integrates content from and links to social media platforms. We also maintain a presence on social media platforms. Please understand that these platforms are operated by third-parties and that your use of the platforms is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies established by their operators. Information you post on these platforms may, depending on your privacy settings, be publicly visible. We urge you to carefully consider what you post.

#### Social Features on this Website

Some pages on the Website contain social features let you publicly post photos or messages. The information you post can be collected and used by people you do not know. We may also use information you post on these social areas of our Website for promotional purposes. We urge you to carefully consider what you post in social areas.

#### Online Tour Center/Customer Portal

We provide a custom portal for travelers and trip organizers. Trip organizers can access your contact information and your account status. You can also access your personal profile. Trip sponsors and other travelers on your trip can view and post photos, blog entries. Information you post on our portal may be visible to other members of your trip. We urge you to carefully consider what you post.

#### Children

We are committed to preserving online privacy for all of the visitors to our Website, including children. Our website is not designed for children and we do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13 without the consent of their parent or guardian.

#### Security 

We have taken reasonable steps and have in place appropriate security measures to protect your personal information, including keeping your financial information private and safe. You acknowledge, however, that no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, despite our efforts. We cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third-parties.  
International Users

If you are visiting our Website from outside of the United States or otherwise contacting us from outside of the United States, please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using our services or purchasing our products, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third-parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### International Users

If you are visiting our Website from outside of the United States or otherwise contacting us from outside of the United States, please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using our services or purchasing our products, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third-parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request certain information from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship. This information includes:

(a)    a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, e-mail and mailing address and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third-parties (including affiliates of the business that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third-parties’ direct marketing purposes; and  
(b)    the names and addresses of all such third-parties.

To request the above information, please e-mail us at:  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#21484f474e6152555445444f55424855580f424e4c1e5254434b4442551c684f474e534c4055484e4f04131153445054445255)

You may also write us at:  

8 Essex Center Drive  
Peabody, MA 01960

Please reference “California disclosure information” in your message or letter. We will respond to requests for California disclosure information within 30 days following receipt at the e-mail or mailing address stated above. If we receive your request at a different e-mail or mailing address, we will respond within a reasonable period of time not to exceed 150 days. Please note that we are only required to respond to each customer once per calendar year.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be either posted on our Website, brochure and/or made available on request. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party. 

#### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or would like to learn more about how we protect privacy, please contact us at:

8 Essex Center Drive  
Peabody, MA 01960  
Toll Free: 1-877-472-3248  
Fax: 1-978-573-2069

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#ec85828a83ac9f9899888982988f859895c28f8381d39f998e86898f98d1a5828a839e818d98858382c9dedc9e899d99899f98)

Privacy Policy: last updated Nov 18, 2015.
